Okay, Rach, that's muffin
and espresso, $4.50.
Ross, double latte, $2.75.
Chandler, coffee and a scone, $4.25.
And Phoebe, herbal tea, $1.25.
All together that's $12.75.
This coming from the man who couldn't
split our $80 phone bill in half.
How much do I owe you?
That's on the house,
courtesy of Joey Tribbiani.
Great. Well, tell him thanks.
And since Joey seems like
such a nice guy...
maybe we could go out?
He's not used to women
being so forward...
but I could check with him.
He says it's okay.
Great. Thanks. Bye-bye.
How come our stuff isn't free?
It will be when you look like
that in a tight skirt.
I'm getting more dates than ever.
You're only giving free stuff
to the pretty girls?
Joey, that is so gross!
How about a scone on the house, baby?
I'm pretty.
The One With Rachel's Sister
-Hey, does anyone have any gum?
-I do.
Here. Sorry.
Oh, you know what?
No.
Wait a second.
-I know it's in here.
-You know what? I'm good.
Sorry, I guess it's in my big bag.
Say, does anybody have a goldfish?
Why are you here?
Shouldn't you be at work?
They sent me home.
They said I can't work if I'm sick.
-Sorry you're sick.
-I'm not sick!
I don't get sick. Getting sick is
for weaklings, it's for pansies.
No one thinks that you're a pansy...
but we do think
that you need a tissue.
I have not been sick
in over three years.
I think you're sick because
that used to be in your nose.
I'll get tissue.
I don't need a tissue. I'm fine-d.
When you put a D
at the end of fine...
you're not fine.
I'm fine-d.
It's a really hard word to say.
-Yes?
-Hi. Is Rachel here? I'm her sister.
Oh, my God, Jill!
Oh, my God, Rachel!
Oh, my God, introduce us.
This is Chandler.
And you know Monica and Ross.
And that's Phoebe.
And that's Joey.
-How you doing?
-Don't!
Honey, what are you doing here?
Which sister is this?
Is this the spoiled one
or the one that bit her?
Daddy cut me off.
Never mind, I got it.
You know what I said?
I said, "I'll hire a lawyer,
sue you, take all your money...
and cut you off!"
Wow. What did he say?
That he wouldn't pay
for my lawyer.
Then he told me to learn
the value of money...
from the one daughter
he's actually proud of.
Did you hear that?
My dad's proud of me.
-Rach?
-Oh, yeah. Sorry.
Honey, so what did you do
that made Dad cut you off?
Okay, I bought a boat.
You bought a boat?
It wasn't for me,
it was for a friend.
Boy, did we make friends
with the wrong sister.
I knew it was stupid and
I shouldn't have done it...
but she bought me all these CDs
and said I had a cute haircut.
And your daddy didn't understand?
I know, and usually I just cry
and say I'm sorry and he forgives me.
Oh, yes, good criers, the Green girls.
I mean, the Green sisters.
Man, no matter how you say it...
it still sounds like you're
talking about green people.
I'm at rock bottom.
This is the best thing that
could've happened to you.
You've needed to get out on your own.
When I did it, at first I was scared,
but then look at me now.
I am the only daughter
that Dad is proud of.
I can't believe him.
How does he expect me to buy stuff?
Maybe, you know, you
won't buy stuff for a while.
I don't understand.
This is what you'll do.
You're gonna get a job.
You're gonna get an apartment.
And then you will live off
the money that you earn.
Okay, I know this is what you did...
but that doesn't sound like me.
Okay, but it can be. It can be you.
And you can stay with us.
Right, Phoebe?
-Of course, yeah.
-Oh, that's so great!
Okay, I'm really gonna do this.
I don't know how to thank you.
Oh, I like cars.
-You all finished?
-Yes.
Great.
Okay, here are the tips
for this morning.
Jen gets 50, 50 for me
and Joey owes 8 dollars.
-What?
-For all the free food you gave away.
If it's free, how come
you're charging me for it?
We don't give anything away
unless it's a birthday.
What if they came in third
in a modeling contest?
No.
Sorry.
I just had the hardest day.
Some of these are so heavy.
How did you pay? I thought
your dad took your credit card.
I memorized those numbers
when I was 15.
But look at all the cool
make-it-on-my-own stuff I got!
This is my "Please hire me" sweater.
And these are my "Don't you want
to rent me this apartment?" pants.
Charging clothes to your dad doesn't
qualify as making it on your own.
Oh, Mr. Scientist has to get
all technical.
Rachel's not gonna think
it's a good idea.
-So who made her queen of the world?
-I would love that job!
What's going on?
Jill!
Did you shop?
No.
They did.
Yeah, we went shopping!
You went shopping?
Then you came here
and paraded it under Jill's nose...
when you know she's trying to quit.
That's terrible.
Sorry, Jill.
So, what'd you get?
Oh, well, all right. Thank you.
I got this, you know,
"I want a job" sweater.
And then I got..
These are apartment pants.
Apartment pants?
You've never heard of them?
Of course I've heard of them.
Ross, what'd you get?
I got this...
This.
-A pashmina?
-Yeah!
I love these babies.
Really?
What's a pashmina?
It's a rug.
Jill?
I'm sorry, Rachel.
You think that's gonna work on me?
I invented that.
Right! But I am sorry.
It's okay.
One little setback is okay.
-But don't let it happen again, okay?
-Okay.
Now, since Daddy paid for all this
stuff, I should take it all away.
But I'm just gonna take the pashmina.
And the pants.
I'll take it all, because that way,
you'll learn the lesson.
Alrighty.
I'm gonna run a couple of errands
and I will see you at dinner.
She took all my stuff.
Yeah. Everything but
the little blue one.
That's the best one!
Oh, my God. Thank you so much!
Well, hey.
Oh, my gosh, that was so lame.
Like a pashmina could be a rug.
Oh, yeah? How about you
with the "I'm sorry"?
Shut up! I wasn't like that at all.
What about what I said about
the apartment pants? How dumb was l?
-Were you this cute in high school?
-Oh, stop.
-No, you stop.
Why don't I sit here
and then you'll both stop it?
Okay. So, what do you want to do?
Let's do something crazy.
I know, let's rest and drink
lots of fluids.
Okay, I'll rest.
But if I'm going to bed,
then you're coming with me.
See, that would be impossible
to resist if you weren't all...
drippy here.
Are you saying that you don't
want to get with this?
I don't think you should say that
even when you're healthy.
Come on.
Don't take this personally.
I just can't have sex
with a sick person.
I'm with you. I can't have sex with
a sick person either. Disgusting!
But I'm not sick!
Let me prove it to you.
We are two healthy people
in the prime of lime.
See, that's the thing, I would like
to stay in the "prime of lime."
Oh, okay, now I'll do it.
Hey. What's up?
I think there's something
you should know.
Better not be about
the apartment pants.
I just pitched the idea to my boss
at Ralph Lauren and she loved it.
No. It's just, I was...
I was with Ross and Jill
after you left...
and I'm pretty sure I saw
a little spark between them.
-What?
-I mean, it's probably nothing.
But I wanted to warn you
that there might be something.
-With Ross and Jill?
-Yeah.
With Ross and my sister?
With my sister Jill
and my ex-boyfriend Ross?
-Oh, there is no way.
-Okay, then.
Oh, my God! I cannot believe that!
I don't like it when he dates anyone,
but my sister?
Isn't that incest or something?
And they're gonna have sex.
Oh, no! What if he marries her too?
This is just terrible.
And I can't stop it.
I don't own Ross.
And Jill should be able to do
what she wants to do.
Oh, my God, I can't believe Ross
is marrying my little sister.
This is the worst thing that
could've ever happened to me.
But great news about
the apartment pants, huh?
That'll be $3.85.
What? Yesterday you said
I was too pretty to pay.
It's just, I can't,
because my manager said that I..
Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday, dear Annie..
-Amy!
Amy
Happy birthday to you
That's weird,
today's my birthday too.
Not in here, it isn't.
Sorry I'm late. What's up?
I just wanted to see if there were
any leads on the old job front.
No. But I walked past three sales
and didn't go in.
How strong am I?
That is great.
You know who doesn't have to
job-hunt? Ross.
-He works at the university.
-Yeah?
So you guys talked? So you get along?
So you're gonna go out?
Me go out with Ross? No.
God, no.
What would make you think that?
Phoebe...
said she thought she saw something
between you guys.
I mean, he's nice.
He's the kind you're friends with,
but not the kind you date.
He's the kind you date,
because you did. But me?
Not so much.
Oh, not so much. What do you mean?
Is there something wrong with Ross?
No, no, no. He's just...
I don't know.
You know, he's just a little bookish.
Are you saying he's a geek?
You think so too?
No. Ross is not a geek.
Then let's just say
he's not my type.
Handsome is not your type?
Smart, kind, good kisser.
What, those things aren't
on your list?
Ross is great.
You'd be lucky to be with him.
If it means that much,
then I'll ask him out.
Oh, no. That's not what I meant.
You know what? You're right.
He has been really nice to me.
Yeah, but he's not your type.
But maybe that's good.
I'm doing all these different things.
Maybe I should just try
dating a geek too.
Yeah, but you don't want
to try too much too fast.
You remember what happened
to the little girl who...
tried too much too fast, don't you?
What?
She died, Jill.
Chandler!
What is it, honey?
You need some tea? Some soup?
Calling Dr. Big.
Dr. Big to the bed.
Jeez, honey,
I thought you were asleep.
How could I be asleep knowing
that you were in the next room?
I was asleep.
No, honey. You know what's sexy?
Layers.
Layers are sexy.
And blankets are sexy.
And hot-water bottles are sexy.
Get into bed.
I want to prove I'm not sick.
I want to make you feel
as good as I feel.
Would you please get some rest?
I'm fine.
-You're coughing.
-No, I'm not.
No, I'm not, I'm laughing.
-At what?
-Just something I heard before.
-Tell me.
-No, I don't want it to spoil the mood.
Happy birthday to you
-You're paying for that.
-No, it's her birthday.
You've sung "Happy Birthday"
to 20 women today.
You are no longer authorized
to distribute birthday muffins.
Damn it!
Did you tell your sister
to ask me out?
-Well, yeah.
-Oh, wow! I mean, wow.
I think she's cute, but...
I never would've thought of
going out with her. Never!
Really?
But after you said it's okay,
I figured, "Why not?"
Oh, so not really "never."
I have to say you are
a much bigger person than I am.
I mean, after all we've been through.
I wish I had a brother
to reciprocate.
If you ever date Monica,
you have my blessing.
And mine.
Chandler?
I think I'm sick.
Really?
Struck down in the "pribe of libe."
Okay, fine, I admit it.
I feel terrible.
Will you please rub this on my chest?
No, no, no.
You are not getting me this way.
Come on, I really need your help here.
-Fine, I'll rub it on myself.
-Okay.
So you're just kind of
rubbing it on yourself?
-Yeah.
-It's nice.
You kidding me?
Is this turning you on?
Yes.
Is it the rubbing or the smell?
It's all very, very good.
So you want to go...
mix it up?
-Not now, I'm sick.
-Oh, come on, you big faker!
What about never sleeping
with sick people?
Well, that was before
all the vaporizing action.
Okay, if you really
want to have sex.
Worked like a charm.
Why are you here?
This is where Ross and I are meeting
for our date. So, what do you think?
I don't like it.
-Really?
-It's kind of slutty.
It's yours.
Yeah, well, I'm a slut.
Me too.
Hi, Jill.
Hi...
Rachel.
You're not at home,
you're right here.
Yeah, I know.
And I bet you thought it would
be weird. But it's not.
Okay.
So, well, I'll...
I'll have her home by midnight.
Why aren't you home yet?
Is someone there?
Oh, yeah, it's me. Sorry.
What are you doing here?
I'm just looking out your window...
at the view.
What are you guys doing?
We got some vapor rub in some places.
He brought her back to his apartment.
Who?
Is that your sister?
She is a slut!
Ross is on a date with your sister.
How weird is that?
Oh, my God, he's taking off
her clothes!
He's taking off her coat.
Oh, this is just terrible.
Oh, no, it's not. It's a first date.
I'm sure that nothing is gonna...
He's gonna get some.
Of the glare...
from the streetlight
out of his apartment.
You know, so he's closed
the drapes there...
so he can have a nice, pleasant...
conversation with
your little sister.
Well, I'm off to bed.
I don't feel good.
You better not get me sick.
I need some fruit
or some juice or some....
Or some nothing.
There's nothing in here.
Who took our food?
Can I interest you in a slice
of lasagna or a drumstick?
-No, thanks.
-Are you sure? It's on the house.
-How about going out with me Friday night?
-No, thanks.
-What are you gonna do.